<form>
    <field>
        <id>general.enabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Enable this feature</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.language</id>
        <label>The templates language</label>
        <style>selectpicker</style>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Language for the HTML templates access denied page.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.checkip</id>
        <label>Loop prevention</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <style>tokenize</style>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>For loop prevention purposes list all IPs e2g can be reached on Include all e2g host server IPs and any VIP used when when in an array.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.extracheckports</id>
        <label>Extracheckports</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <style>tokenize</style>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <hint>3128</hint>
        <help>By default e2g will loop protect for all ports defined in filterports. If you are using squid in front or other device which re-assigns ports then add the user-facing port(s) to extracheckports</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.transparenthttpsport</id>
        <label>Port for transparent https</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <hint>8443</hint>
        <help>To make work firewall will need to redirect tcp port 443 on routed packets to this port and ssl must be enabled with enablessl = on</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.icapport</id>
        <label>Port for ICAP server</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <hint>1344</hint>
        <help>If defined enables icap server mode</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.proxyip</id>
        <label>IP of upstream proxy</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <style>tokenize</style>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <hint>127.0.0.1</hint>
        <help>If blank e2g will go direct to sites.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.proxyport</id>
        <label>Port of upstream proxy</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <hint>3128</hint>
        <help>The port e2guardian connects to proxy on</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.enablessl</id>
        <label>Enable SSL support</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>This must be present to enable MITM and/or Cert checking</help>
    </field>

    <field>
        <id>general.filterip</id>
        <label>Listen IP</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <style>tokenize</style>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <help>The IP that e2guardian listens on. If left blank e2guardian will listen on all IPs. That would include all NICs, loopback, modem, etc. Normally you would have your firewall protecting this, but if you want you can limit it to a certain IP. If mapportstoips is 'on' you can have the same IP twice so long as it has a different port.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.filterports</id>
        <label>Listen ports</label>
        <type>select_multiple</type>
        <style>tokenize</style>
        <allownew>true</allownew>
        <help>The ports that e2guardian listens to. If both mapportstoips and mapauthtoports are set to 'on' you can specify different authentication mechanisms per port but only if the mechanisms can co-exist (e.g. basic/proxy auth can't)</help>
    </field>

    <field>
        <id>general.cacertificatepath</id>
        <label>CA certificate</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select a Certificate Authority to use. To create a CA, go to <a href="/system_camanager.php">CA Manager</a>.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.certprivatekeypath</id>
        <label>Cert private key</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>The public / private key pair used by all generated certificates. required if ssl_mitm is enabled. <![CDATA[Select a certificate to use. To create a cert, go to <a href="/system_certmanager.php">CA Manager</a>.]]></help>
    </field>

    <field>
        <id>general.reverseclientiplookups</id>
        <label>Reverse lookups for IP lists</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>Reverse lookups for banned and exception IP lists. If set to on, e2guardian will look up the forward DNS for the IP of the connecting computer. If a client computer is matched against an IP given in the lists, then the IP will be recorded in any log entries; if forward DNS is successful and a match occurs against a hostname, the hostname will be logged instead. It will reduce searching speed somewhat so unless you have a local DNS server, leave it off.</help>
    </field>

    <field>
        <id>general.loglevel</id>
        <label>Logging Settings</label>
        <style>selectpicker</style>
        <type>dropdown</type>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.logexceptionhits</id>
        <label>Log Exception Hits</label>
        <style>selectpicker</style>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Log if an exception (user, ip, URL, phrase) is matched and so the page gets let through. Can be useful for diagnosing why a site gets through the filter.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.logadblocks</id>
        <label>Enable logging of "ADs"</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>Enable logging of "ADs" category blocks.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.showweightedfound</id>
        <label>Show weighted phrases found</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>If enabled then the phrases found that made up the total which excedes the naughtyness limit will be logged and, if the reporting level is high enough, reported.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.logclienthostnames</id>
        <label>Log client hostnames</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>Perform reverse lookups on client IPs for successful requests.If set to on, e2guardian will look up the forward DNS for the IP of the connecting computer, and log host names (where available) rather than IPs against requests. This is not dependent on reverseclientiplookups being enabled; however, if it is, enabling this option does not incur any additional forward DNS requests.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.loguseragent</id>
        <label>Log client User-Agent</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>Enable logging of client User-Agent. Some browsers will cause a *lot* of extra information on each line!</help>
    </field>

    <field>
        <id>general.contentscanner</id>
        <label>Enable Clamav scan</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>The antivirus must be installed and the databases updated.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>general.contentscannertimeout</id>
        <label>AV scanner timeout</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
        <help>Timeout value to stop processing (eg AV scanning) the file if it takes too long.</help>
    </field>
</form>
